{
    "name": "Vocabulary",
    "cards": [
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "identity",
            "back": "tożsamość"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "emotions",
            "back": "emocje"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "character",
            "back": "charakter"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "gender",
            "back": "płeć"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "fragile",
            "back": "kruchy"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "appearance",
            "back": "wygląd"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "consciousnessous",
            "back": "świadomość"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "intelligent",
            "back": "inteligentny"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "brave",
            "back": "odważny"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "human"
            ],
            "front": "behavior",
            "back": "zachowanie"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "symptom",
            "back": "objaw"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "disease",
            "back": "choroba"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "treatment",
            "back": "leczenie"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "diagnosis",
            "back": "diagnoza"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "prescription",
            "back": "recepta"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "recovery",
            "back": "powrót do zdrowia"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "infection",
            "back": "infekcja"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "immune system",
            "back": "układ odpornościowy"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "injection",
            "back": "zastrzyk"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "appointment",
            "back": "wizyta (u lekarza)"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "allergy",
            "back": "alergia"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "headache",
            "back": "ból głowy"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "cold",
            "back": "przeziębienie"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "fever",
            "back": "gorączka"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "surgery",
            "back": "operacja"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "mental health",
            "back": "zdrowie psychiczne"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "first aid",
            "back": "pierwsza pomoc"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "physician",
            "back": "lekarz"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "painkiller",
            "back": "środek przeciwbólowy"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "health"
            ],
            "front": "check-up",
            "back": "badanie kontrolne"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "occupation",
            "back": "zawód"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "employer",
            "back": "pracodawca"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "employee",
            "back": "pracownik"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "job interview",
            "back": "rozmowa kwalifikacyjna"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "salary",
            "back": "wynagrodzenie"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "career",
            "back": "kariera"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "promotion",
            "back": "awans"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "resignation",
            "back": "rezygnacja (z pracy)"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "internship",
            "back": "staż"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "full-time",
            "back": "pełny etat"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "part-time",
            "back": "niepełny etat"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "work remotely",
            "back": "pracować zdalnie"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "deadline",
            "back": "termin wykonania"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "colleague",
            "back": "współpracownik"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "boss",
            "back": "szef"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "experience",
            "back": "doświadczenie"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "responsibility",
            "back": "odpowiedzialność"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "skills",
            "back": "umiejętności"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "work"
            ],
            "front": "job advertisement",
            "back": "oferta pracy"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "culture"
            ],
            "front": "heritage",
            "back": "dziedzictwo"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "culture"
            ],
            "front": "tradition",
            "back": "tradycja"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "culture"
            ],
            "front": "custom",
            "back": "zwyczaj"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "culture"
            ],
            "front": "festival",
            "back": "festiwal"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "culture"
            ],
            "front": "ritual",
            "back": "rytuał"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "culture"
            ],
            "front": "belief",
            "back": "przekonanie"
        },
        {
            "tags": [
                "vocabulary"
            ],
            "topics": [
                "culture"
            ],
            "front": "language",
            "back": "jezyk"
        }
    ]
}